<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<!-- Pedia text (historical context) about the new building. -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_BUILDINGS_PAGE_BUILDING_TEAHOUSE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>一张屏风和几套桌椅，一个说书人和一壶好茶。茶室是包括岩王帝君在内的璃月人都喜欢光顾的地方。除了评书之外，要是遇上了云堇上戏台的日子，闻名而来的看客能把小小的茶馆里三层外三层围得水泄不通。</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Leader specific pedia text. -->
		<!-- 领袖特性概要 -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KEQING_CHAPTER_CAPSULE_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Keqing and the workers she is leading are impressively productive. They will make use of every inch of land under their foot.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- 领袖玩法介绍 -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KEQING_CHAPTER_DETAILED_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Liyue with Keqing's lead can expand and develop massive amount of tiles effectivly, and settlers with quick movement can reach important stategic location ahead of any one else.[NEWLINE]With the support of Ganyu, Liyue has world leading ability of trading and economic.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Leader specific historical text. -->
		<!-- 领袖历史背景 -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KEQING_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Yuheng of the Liyue Qixing. Keqing has much to say about Rex Lapis' unilateral approach to policymaking in Liyue — but in truth, gods admire skeptics such as her quite a lot.[NEWLINE]One of the Liyue Qixing, Keqing has an uncompromising belief in actions over words. If she sees something that needs doing, she'll do it herself. For example, she traveled around Liyue and carefully memorized each detail of the land so that she may one day be able to maximize the utility of every last inch of Liyue.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KEQING_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Keqing deals with the day-to-day affairs of Liyue, whether great or small, while Rex Lapis only descends once a year.[NEWLINE]To many, the millennia of prosperity that Liyue has enjoyed serve to legitimize Rex Lapis' guidance of the city. But Keqing has her reservations about all this, viewing Liyue's present prosperity as akin to a magnificent sandcastle on the beach — humanity does not have the luxury of deciding when the tide will come in.[NEWLINE]"Rex Lapis has watched over Liyue for a millennium. But what about the next millennium? What about the next ten, or the next hundred millennia? How long are we expecting this status quo to last?"[NEWLINE]It is this unanswered question that drives Keqing to work relentlessly and remain diligent.[NEWLINE]From most people's perspective, there is no point in working oneself up like this. But Keqing cannot sit by idly and ignore this hidden danger.[NEWLINE]The people of Liyue have never considered navigating the future on their own terms. But someone must walk on the front line of the epoch and forge a new path with their own hands.[NEWLINE]From most people's perspective, there is no point in working oneself up like this. But Keqing cannot sit by idly and ignore this hidden danger.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KEQING_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Rex Lapis' departure has put Liyue Harbor through a great deal of hardship. All the duties Rex once fulfilled have been taken up by the Qixing and the Eight Trades.[NEWLINE]Now that divine rule is a thing of the past, the old strictures left behind can't simply be continued wholesale. But to establish new laws for Liyue, whose history spans several thousand years, is no mean feat.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_KEQING_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>At first, Keqing was incredibly enthusiastic about this task, having long prepared for this day when she might finally show her mettle. But several months in, and she was still stuck on a single task, land infrastructure — and it was driving her up the wall.[NEWLINE]No matter how hard she struggled, the mountain of tasks was like a quagmire. She was making a difference, yes, but not nearly with as much ease as Rex Lapis.[NEWLINE]"Why can I only do this much? Why... can't I do it better?"[NEWLINE]Of course, she had long understood the wherefores here.[NEWLINE]Her lack of respect for the gods had somehow received their recognition all the same, yes, but that didn't mean that she was ready to simply replace them.[NEWLINE]But she was still Keqing, resolute and tenacious. From that day on, she shut herself in, studying classics of various kinds to learn all that she needed. Placing herself lowest, she accepted all that she had hitherto not known with open arms.[NEWLINE]During this period, she gained a certain calm, slowly discarding the "opprobrium" she had long held against Rex Lapis. They were both working for the good of Liyue, after all — and two people who love the same thing need not be on opposing sides.[NEWLINE]She also seemingly came to an understanding concerning the smile Rex Lapis had given her during the Rite of Descension. It was, Keqing now believes, an expression of acknowledgement and expectation.[NEWLINE]She hasn't lost any of her forceful and decisive manner, no. But sometimes, when she feels lost, she will stop and think: "What would Rex Lapis do at a moment such as this?"</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Leader specific pedia text. -->
		<!-- 领袖特性概要 -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_NINGGUANG_CHAPTER_CAPSULE_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ningguang knows everything happening in Liyue harbor, her wealth is unsurpassed in all of Teyvat.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- 领袖玩法介绍 -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_NINGGUANG_CHAPTER_DETAILED_BODY" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ningguang has powerful intelligence and anti-spy abilities, this make sure no one can damage Liyue in dark. As a professional businesswoman, she can earn extra profit from international businesses.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Leader specific historical text. -->
		<!-- 领袖历史背景 -->
		<!--<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_NINGGUANG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>「掌握了璃月港所有秘密的凝光是璃月港最大的秘密。」——璃月七星·开阳星如此评价她。</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_NINGGUANG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>凝光是掌管重权的「璃月七星」之一，居天权星之位，识人心，擅话术。即使在人人经商的璃月港，她也是首屈一指的大商人。[NEWLINE]每个见过凝光的人都会被她惊人的洞察力与过人的头脑折服。不仅如此，凝光的作风也极为独特。[NEWLINE]她斥巨资搜集来大量浮空石制成基盘，又在其上建造出一座空前华美的宫殿。浮空石托起空中幻城，使之终年悬浮在璃月港上空。[NEWLINE]这座宫阁正如凝光本人一般，高不可测，远离众生，却轻易吸引了所有目光。[NEWLINE]震动商界的女富商、孩子们最喜欢的温柔姐姐、玉京台宴会上的名媛、甜食界的鉴赏名家……她是千面佳人，也是一个永远无法读懂的美丽谜题。</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_NINGGUANG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>「凝光大人什么都知道。」外来人常常会被璃月人如此告诫。[NEWLINE]想要钻漏子的商会、某位正在囤积货物的奸商、归港船队携带的违禁私货…对于这些或明或暗的信息，「天权」无一不知。[NEWLINE]某位须弥炼金术士到璃月游学，无意中查阅到黑岩厂十年前一笔夜泊石交易的账目。当夜，凝光的近侍便敲响了他的窗户，请他去「群玉阁」一叙。</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_NINGGUANG_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>生活在璃月，人人都需按规则出牌。规则会保护他们的利益不受侵犯，相应地，违规之人也将受到惩罚。[NEWLINE]这些规则源自璃月守护神「摩拉克斯」制订的古老律法，绝对可靠。璃月数千年历史中，历任「天权」对每条律法逐一修订，使其符合璃月不同阶段的社会需求。这些古老律法被整合成册，附带一本两百七十九页的注释，发放到所有璃月人手中。[NEWLINE]凝光喜欢这样的璃月港。井然的秩序能让商业更具活力，而她又比任何人都更理解秩序的细节。	</Text>
		</Row>-->
		<!-- Civilization specific historical text. -->
		<!-- 文明历史背景 -->
		<!--<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_LIYUE_CL_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>璃月是提瓦特历史最悠久的国家。3700年前，摩拉克斯和仙人签订了契约以保护璃月港，这就是璃月国的成立。</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_LIYUE_CL_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>在璃月港建立很久以前，提瓦特七大魔神还没任职而神灵还自由地在世上漫游的时间，这片将会成为璃月的土地上存有很多村庄。在这个时代，摩拉克斯和尘土之神归终共同管治现在名为“归离原”的地方。 这个文明在他们的共同统治和在仙人的保护下变得繁荣昌盛。</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CIVILIZATIONS_PAGE_CIVILIZATION_LIYUE_CL_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>魔神战争爆发时，这个文明经过了激烈战争后被摧毁，也导致了归终的死亡；本来肥沃的荻花州变成了一片沼泽。摩拉克斯带他的人民向南，在天衡山南边建立璃月港，直到今日。为了保护这新的城市，摩拉克斯与仙人签订了契约，自己就去与其他恶神作战。在镇压了数个魔神，如“漩涡之魔神”，以及其他魔神的死去（如“盐之魔神”赫乌莉亚) 后，摩拉克斯成为璃月战场中的胜者，成为尘世的岩神。一年一度，摩拉克斯在“七星请仙典仪”正式下凡，为璃月人民赐下神谕，指引下一年璃月经营的方向。日常凡务就由璃月七星、商会、和千岩军处理。</Text>
		</Row>-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_GANYU_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ganyu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_GANYU_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The secretary of the Liyue Qixing</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_GANYU_SHORT_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The secretary of the Liyue Qixing</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_GANYU_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ganyu is the architect of administrative efficiency.[NEWLINE]She cares of the civilians' livelihood, provides bonus in multiple areas.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_GOVERNOR_GANYU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Drink only spring water, eat only whole grain. Proceed with elegance, avoid certain peril.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_GOVERNOR_GANYU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>For the Liyue Qixing of the lofty Yujing Terrace, Ganyu is not merely a companion to serve them, but is instead coordinator of the web of information that moves across Liyue Harbor, and the architect of administrative efficiency.[NEWLINE]Complex meeting minutes, disorderly report data... Every day piles of documents flow by like water, each one personally compiled by her into clear and concise words in order to assist the Qixing's every decision and negotiation as they flow through various organizational departments.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_GOVERNOR_GANYU_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In the eons that have gone by, the Qixing have changed with each succession of their posts, while only Ganyu has lived to see the flourishing of Liyue Harbor from beginning to the modern day.[NEWLINE]The human blood that runs through her veins makes her reluctant to leave the splendor of the city lights, while her adeptus side leads her to yearn for the gentle serenity of her adeptal homeland.[NEWLINE]For the half-human, half-adeptus Ganyu, between the bustling sea of people and the ethereal clustered peaks, which is more fitting to call home?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_MIND_IN_CIVIL_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mind in civilians</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_MIND_IN_CIVIL_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Returns to her work in no time. +3[ICON_Amenities]Amenities。</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_MIND_IN_CIVIL_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>As the secretary of Yuehai Pavilion, Ganyu undertakes many tasks that ordinary folk do not see. The calculations and data behind the Qixing's every decision in Liyue, as well as every ordinance and regulation that is announced, are all the meticulous work of Ganyu.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_MIND_IN_CIVIL_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Each daybreak she stands by the dock, enjoying her breakfast in silence. Even still, by the time the sun has fully risen, she will have returned to Yuehai Pavilion overlooking Yujing Terrace, to continue to fulfill her contract — one that she signed three thousand years ago with Rex Lapis.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SECRETARY_FOR_QIXING_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Decision helper</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SECRETARY_FOR_QIXING_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Provide unique ability according to Leader.(Details in Civilopidia)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SECRETARY_FOR_QIXING_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>"Decision helper" provides one of the following bonuses according to Leader: [NEWLINE]For Keqing: +1 Road Level, enable using builders to help constuct districts.[NEWLINE]For Ningguang: 20% discount when purchasing districts, buildings, units in this city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_SECRETARY_FOR_QIXING_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>They are aware that the Liyue Qixing are the cream of the crop who hold the fate of the city in their hands, but the calculations and data behind the Qixing's every decision are far harder to grasp.[NEWLINE]The people understand that the new policies announced each year will change the dynamics of the market, yet none can comprehend how policy is plucked from complex meeting minutes and compiled into something easier on the human eye.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_FROSTFLAKE_ARROW_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Frost flake arrow</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_FROSTFLAKE_ARROW_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>City +10[ICON_Ranged]ranged attack strength，and one extra[ICON_Ranged]shot.[NEWLINE]Ranged units trained in this city gets free promotion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_FROSTFLAKE_ARROW_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_FADE_IN_HUMAN_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Fade in human</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_FADE_IN_HUMAN_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Provide fresh water for the city. +3[ICON_Food]food for improved crop resource in the city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_FADE_IN_HUMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>How long is a thousand years?[NEWLINE]Long enough for the Glaze Lilies that once teemed throughout Dihua Marsh to be wiped out by floodwaters, and long enough for the thriving settlement that sprung up upon Guili Plains to come to ruin in war.[NEWLINE]How short is a thousand years?[NEWLINE]To Ganyu, it has felt shorter than the blink of an eye.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_FADE_IN_HUMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Throughout a passage of time unimaginable to mortals, Ganyu has been working on all manner of things at Yujing Terrace.[NEWLINE]She recorded the raising and demolishing of every building, and witnessed the rise to prosperity of every industry.[NEWLINE]Ganyu's sense of objectivity towards the passage of time comes from the endless reams of data she must trawl through, and from the ever-increasing number of colors she finds that she needs to categorize it all.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_FADE_IN_HUMAN_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>All this time, her mindset has never changed — she constantly wavers between her human and adeptus halves.[NEWLINE]On one hand, Ganyu the qilin finds it difficult to comprehend mortal squabbles. But on the other hand, her human blood reminds her always to hold out hope that she might someday be able to fit in.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_PROSPEROUS_PEACE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Prosperous peace</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_PROSPEROUS_PEACE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Extra available district in city，and the availability to purchase using[ICON_Gold]Gold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_PROSPEROUS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_RESOURCE_STACKING_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Resource allocating</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_RESOURCE_STACKING_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Regional effect from buildings can now spread 6 tiles further. Allow the city to receive[ICON_Production]production bonus from multiple industrial districts.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_PAGE_GOVERNOR_PROMOTION_RESOURCE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Civlization Citizen Names -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jiayi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hongyi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Suling</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yanxiao</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Qiang</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Zhonglin</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Zhihua</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Zhuyu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Bibo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Shun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_11" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Kuan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_12" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Fengyan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_13" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hongru</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_14" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gui</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_15" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Zhenhai</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_16" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Dongsheng</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_17" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Shitou</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_18" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Xu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_19" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Degui</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_MALE_20" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Bolai</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Qiming</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Changshun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ziwei</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Xiling</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Huixing</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wuyuan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Xiuhua</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_8" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yinxing</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_9" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Huangshan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_10" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tiantian</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_11" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Baixiao</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_12" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_13" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jifang</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_14" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ruoxin</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_15" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gongming</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_16" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Linlang</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_17" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Luoxia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_18" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Huixin</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_19" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Xingxi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITIZEN_LIYUE_FEMALE_20" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yueshu</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Civilization City Names-->
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_LIYUE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Liyue</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_TIANHENG" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tian Heng</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_DIHUA" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Di Hua</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_WANGSHU" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wang Shu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_QINGCE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Qing Ce</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_JUEYUN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Jue Yun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_BISHUI" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Bi Shui</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_STONE_GATE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Stone Gate</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_WUWANG" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Wu Wang</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_SAL_TERRAE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Sal Terrae</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_MINLIN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Min Lin</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_CUIJUE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Cui Jue</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_HUAGUANG" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hua Guang</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_AOCANG" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ao Cang</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_HULAO" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Hu Lao</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_NANTIANMEN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Nan Tian Men</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_QINYUN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Qing Yun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_TIANQIU" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Tian Qiu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_QIONGJI" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Qing Ji</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_GUILI" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gui Li</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_MINGYUN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ming Yun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_YAOGUANG" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yao Guang</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_LUHUA" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Lu Hua</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_LISHA" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Li Sha</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_DUNYU" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Du Yu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_LINGJU" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Ling Ju</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_QINGXU" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Qing Xu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_YUNLAI" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Yun Lai</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_GUYUN" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Gu Yun</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CITY_NAME_THE_CHASM" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Chasm</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!--Civilization Factoids -->
		<!-- 地理环境与社会数据 -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_LIYUE_LOCATION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Location</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_CIVINFO_LIYUE_LOCATION_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Teywat</Text>
		</Row>

		<!-- Leader Quotes -->
		<!-- 领袖名言 -->
		<Row Language="en_US" Tag="LOC_LEADER_KEQING_QUOTE"
			 Text="If you feel strongly about something, you should speak up and take action. That's the philosophy I live by."
/>
		<!--first meet-->
		<Row Language="en_US" Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_LEADER_KEQING_ANY"
			Text="I am Keqing, Yuheng of the Liyue Qixing. My role is to manage real estate and construction in Liyue."
/>
		<Row Language="en_US" Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_VISIT_RECIPIENT_LEADER_KEQING_ANY"
			Text="Liyue is a vast place with abundant resources. I will show you around. You deserve to see Liyue cities with your own eyes."
/>
		<Row Language="en_US" Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NEAR_INITIATOR_POSITIVE_LEADER_KEQING_ANY"
			Text="Let's go, time is against us."
/>
		<Row Language="en_US" Tag="LOC_DIPLO_FIRST_MEET_NO_MANS_INFO_EXCHANGE_LEADER_KEQING_ANY"
			Text="Would you like some kindly exchange of capital information? In return, I will show you around when you come to see our capital Liyue one day."
/>
		<!--deligation-->
		<Row Language="en_US" Tag="LOC_DIPLO_ACCEPT_DELEGATION_FROM_HUMAN_LEADER_KEQING_ANY"
			Text="Accepted. I like you as you make up your own mind."
/>
		
		<!-- Leader Quotes -->
		<!-- 领袖名言 -->
		<Row Tag="LOC_LEADER_NINGGUANG_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>赌徒永远会把希望寄托在下一颗骰子上。但最后赚钱的，当然是从来不碰骰子的庄家。</Text>
		</Row>

	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>